So a few hours ago I called crisis services, I was genuinely considering killing myself and had
nobody to talk to and just needed a voice and somebody to listen. They said they'd send a
volunteer to take me to get help and they'd meet me at the corner of my street so my roommates
wouldn't have to know. I get there, there's cops waiting they get out walk up ask to see my hands
while reaching for handcuffs, I look around there's cop cars coming fire trucks and they're
all reaching for batons or flashlights or handcuffs. So I obviously fucking run,
im hiding behind cars and in between houses there at my house talking to my roommates about me,
I had to sneak in a side door and hide in the attic since it's snowing.
I finally found a place I can go to for counseling tomorrow. But when somebody asks for help why do
they pull up like I belong in prison and go for batons I called for help not to get fucking jumped
by police or arrested. Everyone sees me as crazy now and I get why, I just wish they would see it
through my eyes and not belittle me for it. Just to be clear im good rn not really looking for a
pity party, processing everything and found a place to go for counseling and maybe some
antidepressants and mood stabilizers tomorrow. Just need to find somewhere else to live,
im way too embarrassed to leave my room at all and show my face to anyone I know.
This has just been a wild night.